{
    "subject": "resource/Samoan_crisis",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Samoan Crisis",
    "human_readable": "The name of Samoan crisis is Samoan Crisis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9716595411300659,
            "question": "What is the name of the Samoan crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9491497278213501,
            "question": "Is there a specific event referred to as the 'Samoan Crisis'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819933533668518,
            "question": "Is the term 'Samoan Crisis' used exclusively for this specific event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676652312278748,
            "question": "What were the consequences of the Samoan Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8434752225875854,
            "question": "Can you provide details about the Samoan Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7795242071151733,
            "question": "When did the Samoan Crisis occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7486709356307983,
            "question": "What were the causes of the Samoan Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7293154001235962,
            "question": "Were there any key figures involved in the Samoan Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7028368711471558,
            "question": "How is the Samoan Crisis remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.659850001335144,
            "question": "What impact did the Samoan Crisis have on Samoa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Samoan crisis is Samoan Crisis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3818_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Samoan Crisis remembered today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3818_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any key figures involved in the Samoan Crisis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3818_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the causes of the Samoan Crisis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3818_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3818_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided does indeed support that the term \"Samoan Crisis\" refers to the same historical event described in the documents. The documents discuss a military standoff involving the United States, Germany, and Great Britain (British Empire) in Samoa during the late 19th century, which aligns with the name \"Samoan Crisis.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}